# **Amalia Batul Rosyidah**

Surabaya, East Java | +6285 3345 43315 | amaliarosyidah01@gmail.com |linkedin.com/in/amaliabatulrosyidah



#### SUMMARY

I am Amalia Batul Rosyidah, a 20 years old, Surabaya State University student majoring in Special Education. In addition, learn about the barriers of friends with disabilities. I have also been pursuing graphic design since high school until now and have won poster and logo competitions several times. I am interested in the world of graphic design because I have studied design since I was in high school. I also often take part in training programs and design communities to deepen my knowledge regarding graphic design.

#### **EDUCATION**

#### **Universitas Negeri Surabaya**

Surabaya

Bachelor's degree in Faculty of Education, [Special Education]

2021- Present

IPK: 3.85 / 4.0

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

**GudCare** Surabaya

Graphic Designer & Design Marketing – Internship

Agust 2023 - Present

Gudcare is a company that oversees 2 perfume brands Fresh Chubs and Penatu Home

- Make branding design and mockup for Penatu Home product
- Manage instagram design
- Manage e-commerce design (Shoppe, Tokopedia, & Lazada)
- Make Proposal design product

MagangUpdate Jakarta (WFH)

Graphic Designer & Social Media - Internship

Feb 2023 – July 2023

MagangUpdate referring to a media platform internship program or an update program career preparation.

- Make the entire visual design for 3 divisional purposes (Bussines & Patnership Development, Copy Writer, and Web Developer)
- Make visual asset Instagram MagangUpdate for instagram feeds and story
- Make an analysis of the development of social media in MagangUpdate

**Ankaranesia** Work From Home Graphic Designer - Internship Sep 2021 – Jan 2023

Ankaranesia has a Turkish language learning platform that provides online Turkish learning programs

Make visual asset Instagram Ankaranesia for instagram feeds and story

Planning design themes and design signs at Direktorat Disabilitas Programs

Make visual design and merchandise in every event at Ankranesia

## ORGANIZATIONAL EXPERIENCE

Direktorat Disabilitas (Universitas Negeri Surabaya)

Surabaya

Feb 2023 - July 2023

Graphic Designer

- Set the course of the distribution of Design in the team

## **ACHIEVEMENT**

- Presenter at International Conference on Esucation Innovation (7<sup>th</sup> ICEI), Augst 2023
  "The Effect of Class Teachers' Self-Efficacy on Inclusive Education Services for Special Needs Children in Inclusive Schools"
- The Winner Of Divisi Difabel Sayembara Logo Competition, July 2022
- Top 10 National posters "Be Wise in Social Media" By BEM University Of Surabaya, Nov 2021
- National best poster nomination "Nature" By MAPALA Kopasas, July 2021

# **SKILL & COURSES**

## **Google Workspaces**

Google Form; Google Slides; Google Documents; Google Spreadsheet; Google Sites

## Language

Indonesia

English – Level Upper Intermediete English First (EF) (508)

# **Design Application**

Visual - Adobe Illustrator (AI), Photoshop (PS), & Canva